# Lucas D. Batista

Mid. mobile developer

# **Summary**

Passionate and well-qualified mobile developer with more than 5 years of experience. Working with Android and Flutter. Studying Agile, Clean Architecture, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares.

#### Know-how



# Experience



Mid. Android developer at americanas s.a. October 2021 - July 2023



Mid. Flutter developer at Megaleios June 2021 - August 2021



Jr. Flutter developer at Bean Softwares March 2021 - June 2021



Jr. Flutter developer at Thalamus Digital July 2020 - June 2021



Jr. Flutter developer at MFIT Personal January 2020 - May 2020

### **Education**



Computer Science at Univali February 2020 - Present



English at KNN Idiomas October 2020 - October 2022

# **Projects**



April 2021 - Present



Unilovers
February 2022 - July 2023

## **Details**

SC, Brazil

contact@lucasbatista.me

### Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

### **Skills**

**SOLID** 

TDD

Clean Architecture

Refactoring

Scrum

Cloud

**Data Structures** 

Design Patterns

# Languages

English

#### **Hobbies**

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.